<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mustahiq</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">OPEN_DRAWER</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">CLOSE_DRAWER</string>

    <string name="guzara_allownce">GUZARA ALLOWANCE</string>
    <string name="guzara_intro">Guzara allowance is a monthly grant meant for the chronic poor. It aims to safeguard them from hunger which is both cause and manifestation of extreme poverty. Its current monthly rate is Rs. 2000 and is paid by the local Zakat committee of the area of residence of the deserving (Mustahiq) person.</string>
    <string name="elgibelity_head">Eligibility Criteria</string>
    <string name="guzara_eligibility">1.    Istehqaq is determined by Local Zakat Committee of the area of permanent residence of the applicant \n
        2.  Adult Muslim, living below poverty level with preference to widows and disabled. \n
        3.  Unemployed. \n
        4.  Not a habitual beggar</string>
    <string name="how_to_apply_label">How to Apply</string>
    <string name="text_how_to_apply">The deserving person can apply to the Chairman, Local Zakat Committee of the area of his/her residence. Local Zakat Committee, keeping in view of the financial condition of the applicant, may determine or reject his/her Istehqaq. Guzara allowance is paid via cross cheque.  </string>
    <string name="bullets_h_t_apply"> 1. Rs. 415.200 million, 60% of the regular Zakat budget. \n
        2.  Rs. 1,000/- per month per Mustahiq. \n
        3.  34600 No of beneficiaries in the financial year 2016-17. \n
        4.  Istehqaq to provide Zakat assistance is determined by the Local Zakat Committee of the area.</string>
    <string name="marriage_allownce">MARRIAGE ASSISTANCE</string>
    <string name="marriage_intro">The aim of marriage grant is to provide financial assistance to the unmarried women who or their guardians cannot afford marriage expenses. Its current rate is 20,000 PKR.</string>
    <string name="marriage_eligibility">Any poor, needy and deserving woman or her parent/guardian can apply for this grant.</string>
    <string name="text_how_to_apply_mariage">The Mustahiq can apply to Local Zakat Committee for Marriage Assistance. Local Zakat committee will determine Istehqaq and will process to District Zakat Committee which will release funds as per procedure to the Local Zakat Committee concerned. Payment will be made by Local Zakat Committee.</string>
    <string name="education_general_allownce">EDUCATIONAL STIPENDS GENERAL</string>
    <string name="edu_general_intro">Educational Stipend (general) is meant to provide financial assistance to the deserving students in order to help them continue their studies.</string>
    <string name="edu_general_eligibility">Stipends are provided to the poor and deserving students studying in such colleges, universities, polytechnic and other educational and professional institutions in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa that are established or recognized by the Government. Istehqaq is determined by Local Zakat Committees and endorsed by the scholarship committee of the educational institute. Scholarship committee comprises Head of Institution, Class Teacher and a nominee of District Zakat Committee.</string>
    <string name="text_how_to_apply_edu_general">A deserving student can apply to the head of the institution which will process it after determination of Istehqaq by the local Zakat committee. Funds are released by the District Zakat Committee to the concerned educational institution which will make payment to the student.</string>
    <string name="edu_professional_allownce">EDUCATIONAL STIPENDS – TECHNICAL</string>
    <string name="edu_prof_intro"><![CDATA[In order to make the poor youth an earning hand, Zakat & Ushr department has initiated a special program. Through this comprehensive program, students are given free technical training in market-oriented trades through well-known technical vocational institutions of the Districts. During the training, Rs. 2000/- per month is given to each trainee and Rs. 8,000/- for the purchase of tools along with course completion certificate are also given at the end of their successful training.]]></string>
    <string name="edu_prof_eligibility">Istehqaq is determined by Local Zakat Committees and endorsed by the scholarship committee of the educational institute comprising Chairman District Zakat Committee, District Zakat Officer, Principal Vocational Training Institute, a Class Teacher and one member District Zakat Committee.</string>
    <string name="text_how_to_apply_edu_prof">The student can apply to the District Zakat Committee on the prescribed form for Stipends Technical through his/her institution, subject to a determination of Istehqaq by the Local Zakat Committee concerned. The District Zakat Committee releases funds to the Technical institutions for stipends to deserving students.</string>
    <string name="education_general_allownce_u">تعلیمی گرانٹ (عام)</string>
    <string name="edu_general_intro_u">تعلیمی وظیفہ (عام) کا مقصد مستحق طلباء کو اپنی تعلیم جاری رکھنے میں مدد کے لئے مالی اعانت فراہم کرنا ہے</string>
    <string name="elgibelity_head_u">اہلیت کا معیار</string>
    <string name="edu_general_eligibility_u">خیبر پختونخوا میں ایسے کالجوں ، یونیورسٹیوں ، پولی ٹیکنک اور دیگر تعلیمی اور پیشہ ورانہ اداروں میں تعلیم حاصل کرنے والے غریب اور مستحق طلباء کو وظیفہ فراہم کیا جاتا ہے جو حکومت کے ذریعہ قائم یا تسلیم شدہ ہیں۔ استحاق کا تعین مقامی زکوٰ کمیٹیوں کے ذریعہ کیا جاتا ہے اور تعلیمی انسٹیٹیوٹ کی اسکالرشپ کمیٹی نے اس کی تائید کی ہے۔ اسکالرشپ کمیٹی میں ہیڈ آف انسٹی ٹیوشن ، کلاس ٹیچر اور ڈسٹرکٹ زکوٰ کمیٹی کا نامزد کیا گیا ہے</string>
    <string name="how_to_apply_label_u">درخواست دینے کا طریقہ</string>
    <string name="text_how_to_apply_edu_general_u">ایک مستحق طالب علم اس ادارے کے سربراہ کے لئے درخواست دے سکتا ہے جو مقامی زکوٰ  کمیٹی کے ذریعہ استحقاق کے عزم کے بعد اس پر عملدرآمد کرے گا۔ ضلعی زکوٰ کمیٹی کے ذریعہ فنڈز متعلقہ تعلیمی ادارے کو جاری کردیئے گئے ہیں جو طالب علم کو ادائیگی کریں گے</string>
    <string name="translate_into_english">Translate to English</string>
    <string name="translate_into_urdu">Translate to Urdu</string>
    <string name="edu_professional_allownce_u">تعلیمی گرانٹ (پیشہ ور)</string>
    <string name="edu_prof_intro_u"><![CDATA[غریب نوجوانوں کو کمائی کا ہاتھ بنانے کے لئے ، محکمہ زکوٰ & اور عشر نے ایک خصوصی پروگرام شروع کیا ہے۔ اس جامع پروگرام کے ذریعہ طلباء کو اضلاع کے مشہور تکنیکی پیشہ ور اداروں کے ذریعہ مارکیٹ پر مبنی تجارت میں مفت تکنیکی تربیت دی جاتی ہے۔ تربیت کے دوران ، روپے 2000 / - ماہانہ ہر ٹرینی کو دیا جاتا ہے اور 500 روپے۔ 8،000 / - ٹولز کی خریداری کے ساتھ کورس کی تکمیل کا سرٹیفکیٹ بھی ان کی کامیاب ٹریننگ کے اختتام پر دیا جاتا ہے۔]]></string>
    <string name="edu_prof_eligibility_u">استحاق کا تعین مقامی زکوٰ کمیٹیوں کے ذریعہ کیا جاتا ہے اور چیئرمین ڈسٹرکٹ زکوٰ کمیٹی ، ڈسٹرکٹ زکا Officer آفیسر ، پرنسپل ووکیشنل ٹریننگ انسٹی ٹیوٹ ، کلاس ٹیچر اور ایک ممبر ڈسٹرکٹ زکوٰ کمیٹی پر مشتمل تعلیمی انسٹی ٹیوٹ کی اسکالرشپ کمیٹی کے ذریعہ اس کی تائید ہوتی ہے۔</string>
    <string name="text_how_to_apply_edu_prof_u">طالب علم اپنے ادارہ کے توسط سے اسٹیکنڈس ٹیکنیکل کے ل form ڈسٹرکٹ زکوٰ to کمیٹی میں درخواست دے سکتا ہے ، جو متعلقہ مقامی زکوat کمیٹی کے ذریعہ استحاق کے تعین کے تحت ہے۔ ضلعی زکوٰ Committee کمیٹی تکنیکی طلبہ کو مستحق طلباء وظائف کے لئے فنڈز جاری کرتی ہے۔</string>
    <string name="introduction"><![CDATA[The Government of Pakistan introduced Zakat system in the country for the first time in 1980 through an Ordinance. \n \n
     Till 1994, the system worked under the administrative control of provinces. \n \n
     In July, 1994 it was federalized and went  under the direct supervision of Federal Govt: for two and a half years. \n \n
     In 1997, the centralized control of the Federal Govt: was done away with and operations of Zakat system was entrusted to Provincial Zakat Administrations.  \n \n
     In the wake of 18th constitutional amendment, Zakat system was devolved to the Provinces. Certain matters already being dealt with by the Ministry of Zakat and  Ushr have been transferred to Zakat & Ushr Department, Khyber Pakhtunkhwa]]></string>
    <string name="title_activity_district_zakat_detail">DistrictZakatDetail</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dzo_label">DZO:</string>
    <string name="label_no_lzcs">No of LZC:</string>
    <string name="label_list_of_zakat">List of Local Zakat Committees</string>
    <string name="tehsil_label">Tehsil:</string>
    <string name="label_chairman">Chairman:</string>
    <string name="focal_person">Focal Person:</string>
    <string name="contact_number">Contact No:</string>
    <string name="text_to_call">This action will let you contact the listed focal person.</string>
    <string name="proceed_text">Do you want to proceed?</string>
    <string name="introduction_app">Mustahiq application is an informatory platform for public awareness about different Schemes of Zakat and Ushr Department. \n \n
        The application include information about District Zakat Committees (DZC) and Local Zakat Committees (LZC) within districts with focal person contact numbers \n \n
        The application also list provincial hospitals list from where public can get relief using Zakat and Ushr Department schemes \n \n
        Furthermore the application include list of schemes currently offered by Zakat and Ushr department for financial assistance to needy."</string>
    <string name="deeni_madaris">Deeni Madaris</string>
    <string name="deeni_madaris_intro"><![CDATA[Educational Stipend (Deeni Madaris) is provided to the deserving students acquiring religious education. The aim is to help them continue their studies in accordance with the Islamic tenets and not to indulged in anti-state or anti-society activities. It includes a grant for the Madrasa administration to meet accommodation and food expenses of the students.  \n \n
    Rates of the scholarships are as under:- \n
    \tDarja Salasa, Saniya and Arba: \n
     \t\t\t\tRs.2000/- per month. \n
    \tDarja Khamsa, Sadsa, Mokof e Alyh and Dura Hades: \n \t\t\t\tRs.3000/- per month.]]></string>
    <string name="deeni_madaris_eligibility">Stipends are provided to the deserving students studying in Deeni Madaris which are registered with Zakat Department and are cleared from the Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Home Department. Istehqaq of students is determined by Local Zakat Committees and endorsed by the scholarship committee of the Deeni Madaris comprising Head of Institution, class teacher and nominee of District Zakat Committee.</string>
    <string name="text_how_to_apply_deni_madaris">A deserving student can apply to the head of the institution (Mohtamim) which will process it after determination of Istehqaq by the local Zakat committee. Funds are released by the District Zakat Committee to the concerned Deeni M</string>
    <string name="health_care_a">Health Care (District Level)</string>
    <string name="health_care_a_intro">This is a health safeguard for poor patients who cannot afford expenses for their treatment. Zakat funds for medical treatment of the deserving (Mustahiq) patients are provided to district headquarters hospitals and tehsil headquarter hospitals of Government of Khyber Pakhtunkhwa. \n \n
        The patients are provided health care as per following expenses: \n
        Indoor patients \t\t\t\tRs. 8,000/- per visit \n
        Outdoor patients \t\t\t\tRs. 4,000/- per visit</string>
    <string name="health_care_b">Health Care (Provincial Level)</string>
    <string name="health_care_b_intro">Rs. 71.00 million were allocated during the financial year 2017-18 for the Provincial level major hospitals in the Province. Patients are provided health care as per following expenses: \n\n
        Indoor patients \t\t\t\tRs. 10,000/- per visit \n
        Outdoor patients \t\t\t\tRs.   5,000/- per visit</string>
    <string name="health_care_eligibility">Istehqaq is determined by the local Zakat committee of the area of permanent residence of the patient.</string>

</resources>
